Animation Editor Modification
The animation editor in Marvelous Designer 11 is located at the bottom of the screen.
Click the triangle to see the animation editor interface.
In the previous version of Marvelous Designer, some of the details on the top of the animation editor are now moved to the right.
But you can still find a few tools that are commonly used at the top, such as recording, playback and simulation quality.
The most prominent advantage of the animation editor is the FPS setting.
In the previous version, FPS must be set every time you import a file.
But now use Marvelous Designer 11.
You can set the FPS in the animation settings.
Open the animation settings.
On the top, there will be a frame rate setting.
In Marvelous Designer 11, only the set playback area can be recorded and played.
You can set the playback area by dragging the mouse to the two ends of the yellow bar at the top of the animation layer and dragging the mouse to set the playback area.
Or you can directly enter the starting and ending frames in the quick menu.
There are three options for simulation quality.
Normal, animation and self-defining.
You can usually use the normal option to test the animation.
Use the animation option for final recording.
If you want to use a more complex simulation quality, you can enter a number greater than 6 in the preset attribute bar on the right.
You can control the width of the animation bar by controlling the bottom slider.
Click and drag the left slider to the left.
You can widen the area on the left.
Click and drag the right slider to the right.
You can widen the area on the right.
When you click and drag the middle part of the slider, you can adjust the entire animation to any side.
You can also enter the number in the input box on the left and right sides of the slider to set the viewing area of the animation axis.
In Marvelous Designer 11, you can use the number of pixels.
This is a function that was not available in the previous version.
You can use the number in the input box on top of the image.
You can choose which image to use.
You can also choose to use the number on top of the image.
Here you can see the number on top of it.
When you click and drag, you can adjust the image to see the image.
If you click and drag the right slider, you can set the voice.
You can assign a departure position to the lights and lights in the image.
In the right panel, you can choose to set the character position.